[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Is it just an emotional pain or is it also a medically diagnosable physical pain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, it is a physical pain as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "When was the last time you said, \"hello\" to a stranger passing you on the street, to a friend you hadn't seen in years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NN", "''", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Hi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Does she do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Have you have periods of genuine loneliness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "I actually did because there is a difference between being alone and being lonely, don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Sanjay, have you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Yeah, I've had periods where I've been lonely, you know, and I think that, you know, you go through periods of life where you're very busy and so you don't recognize it as much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Can you be lonely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Yeah, you see, I think that's a really interesting point because there must be degrees of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "There's loneliness from mourning a loved one, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "To work from home, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Yeah, you can work from -- you can do that and you realize that you haven't spoken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gayle"]}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "When was the last time you said \"hello\" to somebody you didn't know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "NN", "''", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "I'm about to do just that, Gayle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Hello.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "I know, wasn't that nice of me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "You were.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Have you had periods of real genuine loneliness in your life do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "I mean how long could you go without any other contact?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Piers, she could live in a house and never turn on a TV.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I can't imagine but it's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rita Wilson"]}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "``", "NNP", "''", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 265, "question": "What is -- from your point of view, the key points of this campaign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "The key point is to let people know that there is power and you're being able to just say, \"Hello\", thank you Rita Wilson for that.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "She did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "From your experience at social media, is it a force for good or is it also in some way a cover for people perhaps not to interact in the way you just suggested?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Oh, I think it's both and I think it's certainly is a tool that if you choose to use it as force for good, you can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "... I was in town and Gayle, didn't I e-mail you like three to four times?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gayle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "How is your British accent coming along Oprah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Well, it's not that good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Did he say that to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Or is a personal interaction of hearing a voice, seeing somebody, shaking your hand, saying hello, like you said, actually in the end more important?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Well, I think that it depends upon what you're talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBG", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Do you have a lot -- have real screaming argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBP", "JJ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Oh, screaming is not a part of my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "No, I don't scream at anybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Only two people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "In my entire life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Are you a screamer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, I screamed at more than two people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Does that surprise you Oprah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Yes, it's amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Sanjay, what is the -- if you know somebody that you think is lonely, what is the best way to try and make them less lonely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Well, you know...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Other than just saying hello, what else could be done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "You know, don't minimize just saying hello.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 469, "question": "ING: Oprah, where are you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "... absolute stuff...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "I'm going home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "And I, you know, I just want to echo what you've said that it starts with hello and being able to extend your self, I think for everybody who's watching around the world -- Piers, isn't this amazing, you're around the world every night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Hi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Do you have a table for dinner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Certainly, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "How many in your party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I'm alone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Don't you think Sanjay?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Is a loner the same as somebody who is lonely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Not necessarily.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay"]}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "What was it about that feeling of loneliness, that desperation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "And you can't help thinking Sanjay that if people are able to pick on people and -- who are behaving in that way who appeared to be loners and try and interact with them, I'm sure they do, but if tried harder, you could perhaps avoid some of this trying to this happening because it's the disconnection.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Gayle, what do think of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, you know, what I think, I think in this age of Instagram and Twitter, we're always posting all the great stuff we're doing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Why you're lonely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Well, it's really -- it comes about by just everyday hustle and bustle and even though I have a great family and great girl friends, I think over time we just kind of disconnect ourselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Gayle is it a problem that affects more women than men, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "I think that's a better question for you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Sanjay, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "But I would think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Are you worried?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "What if you're not text savvy at all and you've been excluded from the wider group at school or college or wherever it maybe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "Yes that interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "So it's in the (inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Yes and it's very different than picking up the phone just to be able to see your son's face.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "WP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 701, "question": "What was the joke?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "I said, \"What did one elevator say to the other elevator?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "See, isn't that coming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Well, it's terrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "I would have a follow up to you which is right now, you know, if you're in one of the storm there, just like New York and you have these snow storms, if you're at home on your own, you can't get out for days on end, that, and yourself must make you feel very lonely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "Yeah, you know, it can.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 788, "question": "What about for other people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 789, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140219pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "It's been the first time I really said \"Won't buy\" (ph), isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "''", ":", "NN", ":", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "Yeah, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]